Richard Rodgers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Show Music (Box 1-18, Box 22-45)
  - Manuscripts (Box 1-18)
    - Two by Two (1970) lyrics by Martin Charnin
      - The brother department, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Note: this song was cut from the show, but the music was used in "As far as I'm concerned"; Laid in: typed lyric sheets (2), annotations in pencil; 2 p. each (Box-folder 17/27)
      - The covenant, Holograph sketch in pencil, with lyric; [4] p.; Typed lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/28)
      - Ev'rything that's gonna be has been, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [2] p.; Note: same music as "Poppa isn't Poppa anymore" (Box-folder 17/29)
      - Ev'rything that's gonna be has been, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p.; Note: different version than above (Box-folder 17/29)
      - Forty nights, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Typed lyric sheets (2), annotation in pencil on one; [1] p. each (Box-folder 17/30)
      - Getting married [to a person], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Note: this music was later used with a new lyric by Martin Charnin in "Mama always makes it better" from I Remember Mama; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/31)
      - The gitka's song see: [Two by Two sketchbook]
      - The golden ram, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Laid in: ms. lyric sheet in ink (on back of part of typed script); 3 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/32)
      - The golden ram, Typed lyric sheet; 2 p.; Note: slightly different version than above (Box-folder 17/32)
      - The golden ram, Ms. lead sheet, no lyric; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/32)
      - Hey, girlie, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p. (Box-folder 17/33)
      - Hey, girlie, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; At bottom: "(I Do Not Know a Day) Over"; Typed lyric sheets (2); [1] p. each (Box-folder 17/33)
      - I can't complain, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/34)
      - I do not know a day I did not love you: [I can't remember when], Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [3] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet (crossed out) titled "I can't remember when"; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/35)
      - I do not know a day, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; At bottom: "(Hey, Girlie) Over" (Box-folder 17/35)
      - I do not know a day I did not love you: Love song, Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/35)
      - Ninety again, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; 2 p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 17/36)
      - An old man, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/37)
      - Poppa isn't Poppa anymore, or, Everything that's gonna be has been See also: "Ev'rything that's gonna be has been", Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 17/38)
      - Poppa knows best, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 17/39)
      - Put him away!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p.; Typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (Box-folder 17/40)
      - Something doesn't happen, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 3 p. (Box-folder 17/41)
      - Something doesn't happen, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheets (2), annotations on one in pencil; [1] p. each (Box-folder 17/41)
      - Something that you like, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [4] p.; Uniform title: Something, somewhere (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Something that you like, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet with crossed out title changed to "Something, somewhere," annotations in pencil; [1] p.; Uniform title: Something, somewhere (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Something, somewhere, Typed lyric sheet; [2] p. (Box-folder 17/42)
      - Two by two, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 17/43)
      - Two by two, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 17/43)
      - Two by two, Holograph rhythmic sketch in pencil, with lyric; [1] p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheet; 3 p. (incomplete); Typed lyric sheet; 7 p. (Box-folder 17/43)
      - When it dries see: [Sketches for Two by Two] see: [Lyric sheets for Two by Two]
      - Why me?, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [2] p.; At end: holograph sketch material in pencil; Laid in: 16 measure holograph sketch in pencil, with lyric; Typed lyric sheet; 2 p. (Box-folder 18/1)
      - Without my money, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; On back: 9 measures of sketch material in pencil (crossed out); Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/2)
      - You: Who, Holograph sketch in pencil; [1] p.; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/3)
      - You couldn't please me more, Holograph lead sheet in pencil, no lyric; [1] p.; Note: part of lyric later used in "You could not please me more" from I Remember Mama; Typed lyric sheet; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/4)
      - You have got to have a rudder on the ark, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Laid in: typed lyric sheets (2); 2 p. each (Box-folder 18/5)
      - [Two by Two sketchbook], Holograph sketches in pencil, some with lyrics; [22] p.; Includes: The brother department Forty nights [The Gitka's song]: Gitka The golden ram Hey, girlie I can't complain I do not know a day [I did not love you] Ninety again An old man Poppa isn't Poppa anymore Put him away [Saturday] night (located on p. [3]; perhaps for Saturday Night Around the World) Something doesn't happen [Something, somewhere]: Something that you like" Strength is my weakness (located on p. [2]; from Androcles and the Lion) Two by two" When it dries Without my money You couldn't please me more [You have got to have a] rudder on [the] ark [Unidentified] (Box-folder 18/6)
      - [Lyric sheets for Two by Two], Typed lyric sheets; [5] p. total; Includes: As far as I'm concerned When it dries (Box-folder 18/7)
      - [Song listings with notes]: Typed listings of used and unused lyrics of songs, annotations in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/8)
      - [Playbill]: Playbill for Imperial Theatre, November 1970 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Up Stage and Down (1919) amateur musical comedy, lyrics by Richard Rodgers
      - Prism, plums and prunes, Copyist's ms. piano-vocal score in ink; [2] p.; Lyrics by Benj. M. Kaye (Box-folder 18/10)
    - The Valiant Years (1960) television film
      - The American rifle, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/11)
      - The church; Winston depressed, Holograph piano scores in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Churchill is determined, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Deep sea, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/14)
      - England at play, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Factories -- mechanique, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Flute and Chopin, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/17)
      - France gay, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/18)
      - German band, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/19)
      - German unison, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/20)
      - The home guard, Holograph lead sheet in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/21)
      - A hymn, sort of, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Jolly Churchill, Holograph condensed score in pencil; 2 p.; On back: 3 measure sketch of ending (crossed out) (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Luftwaffe, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Majestic England, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Mare nostram, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Mosquito fleet, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/27)
      - Pastoral, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/28)
      - La patrie, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/29)
      - Return from Dunkirk, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/30)
      - Sea killer, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/31)
      - Ski troops, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [3] p. (Box-folder 18/32)
      - Title; Winston is back in office; Winston is back, Holograph piano score/condensed score in pencil, some words; [3] p. (Box-folder 18/33)
      - Triumph, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/34)
      - Winston depressed see: The church
      - Winston is back see: Title
      - Winston is back in office see: Title
      - [Sketches for The Valiant Years], Holograph sketches in pencil; [4] p.; Includes: The American rifle: Machine gun England at play Factories -- mechanique France [gay] Pastoral Winston depressed (Box-folder 18/35)
    - Victory at Sea (1952) television film
      - Tango, Holograph condensed score sketch in pencil; [2] p.; On p. [3]: crossed out sketch material in pencil; Laid in: [2] p. of holograph sketch material in pencil, [1] p. identified as "Tango"; Uniform title: Beneath the southern cross (Box-folder 18/36)
      - Tango part II, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p.; Note: this music became "No other love" from Me and Juliet; Uniform title: Beneath the southern cross (Box-folder 18/36)
      - Building up theme: mustering of forces See also: "Guadalcanal march", Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p. (Box-folder 18/37)
      - Carriers: on board of a carrier, Holograph short score sketch in pencil; 2 p. (Box-folder 18/38)
      - Death and debris see: Song of the high seas
      - Fiddle and geetar, Holograph piano score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/39)
      - From Naples to Rome, Holograph piano score in pencil; [1] p. (Box-folder 18/40)
      - A march, Holograph lead sheet in ink & pencil, no lyric; [2] p.; Uniform title: Guadalcanal march (Box-folder 18/41)
      - [Guadalcanal march]: 1st [verse?] of Guadalcanal march, Holograph sketch in pencil; [2] p.; Laid in: 4 measure holograph sketch in pencil of second theme; Note: holograph sketch in pencil on p. [1] for "Building up theme" (Box-folder 18/41)
      - Victory hymn, Holograph piano score in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: Hymn of victory (Box-folder 18/42)
      - Landing, Holograph condensed score in pencil; 2 p.; On front: holograph sketch material for "Pearl #4"; On back: unrelated crossed out material (transpositions of simple melody) (Box-folder 18/43)
      - The song of the sea, Holograph condensed score in pencil; 3 p.; On back: sketch material headed "Wir fahren gegen England"; Includes: "Rough sea" "[Death and debris]: Discouragement" "[Submarines in a calm sea]: Still sea"; Uniform title: Song of the high seas (Box-folder 18/44)
      - Submarines in a calm sea see: Song of the high seas
      - Pleasant theme: Hawai[i]an mood, Holograph condensed score in pencil; [2] p.; Uniform title: The sunny Pacific Islands (Box-folder 18/45)
    - Winkle Town (1922) unproduced musical
      - I want a man see: America's Sweetheart see: [M.S. 1] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES
      - Comfort me, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 18/46)
      - One a day, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; Lyric by Lorenz Hart (Box-folder 18/47)
      - Since I remember you, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p.; At end: "Light love song" (Box-folder 18/48)
      - You're too wonderful for me! See also: [M.S. 1] in MISCELLANEOUS SKETCHES, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, no lyric; [4] p. (Box-folder 18/49)
    - You'll Never Know (1921) amateur musical comedy, lyrics by Lorenz Hart
      - I'm broke: duet, Holograph piano-vocal score in ink, lyric in pencil; 3 p.; Note: some instrumentation written in (Box-folder 18/50)
      - Jumping Jack!, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Note: some instrumentation written in (Box-folder 18/51)
      - Just a little lie: dance chorus, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil, lyric in ink; 4 p.; Note: some instrumentation written in (Box-folder 18/52)
      - Mr. Director: dance quartet, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 4 p.; Note: some instrumentation written in (Box-folder 18/53)
      - Virtue wins the day: opening, Holograph piano-vocal score in pencil; 7 p.; On back: instrumentation notes (Box-folder 18/54)
      - When I go on the stage see: [Sketches for One Dam Thing After Another]
  - Full scores (Box 22-45)
    - Allegro (1947) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Allegro ballet: #41, Arranger's holograph (Robert Russell Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 82 p. (Box-folder 22/1)
      - New end Allegro, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [11] p. (a-k) (Box-folder 22/1)
      - Allegro (vocal): #40(a), Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 1-6, 13-14 (Box-folder 22/2)
      - New "Allegro": #40, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 38 p.; On folder: "Finale act 2" (Box-folder 22/2)
      - Annabelle solo: #12, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 30 p. (Box-folder 22/3)
      - Children's dance: #5, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 59 p.; On p. 52: "Children's ballet" (Box-folder 22/4)
      - Come home, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. (Box-folder 22/5)
      - Verse -- Come home, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 4 p. (Box-folder 22/5)
      - End of college dance; Darn nice campus, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 39 p.; Uniform title: A darn nice campus (Box-folder 22/6)
      - Dream sequence: #11, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 23/1)
      - Entr'acte, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 27 p. (Box-folder 23/2)
      - A fellow needs a girl, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 17 p. (Box-folder 23/3)
      - Finale act I, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 54 p. + [1] p. laid in (Box-folder 23/4)
      - Finale ultimo, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 23/5)
      - Freshman get-together: #10, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 11 p. (Box-folder 23/6)
      - The gentleman is a dope, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 26 p. (Box-folder 23/7)
      - I know it can happen again, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 23/8)
      - Intro: I know it can happen again, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [1] p.; On folder: "#2," "#3" and "Pudgy Legs (parts)" (Box-folder 23/8)
      - It may be a good idea for Joe, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 16 p.; Uniform title: It may be a good idea (Box-folder 23/9)
      - Money isn't ev'rything, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 84 p.; Laid in: ozalid piano-vocal score; 9 p.; Includes: "Money utility" "Money dance" (Box-folder 23/10)
      - One foot, other foot, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 21 p. + p. 19a-19b (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Opening, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 36 p. (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Opening act II, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 12 p. + p. a-b (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Overture, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 50 p. + [3] p. laid in; Includes: "Change to college" (Box-folder 24/4)
      - Poor Joe, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 2 p. (Box-folder 24/5)
      - Rotunda, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; [39] p. (numbered variously 1-42); On folder: "#17" (Box-folder 24/6)
      - So far, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 18 p. + [1] p., crossed out, for "So far 1st ending" (Box-folder 24/7)
      - What a lovely day for a wedding, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 33 p. (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Intro. to Lovely day, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink and pencil; p. a-c (Box-folder 24/8)
      - #30: 25, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p.; Note: no obvious relation to above (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Wildcats, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 1 p. (Box-folder 24/9)
      - The wildcats are on a rampage: utility, Ms. full score in ink; 9 p. (Box-folder 24/9)
      - Winters go by, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Yatata, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 33 p. + p. a-c; Note: p. 28-30 were cut and replaced by p. a-c; Uniform title: Yatata, yatata, yatata (Box-folder 25/2)
      - You are never away, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 26 p. (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Never away encore, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink & pencil; 27 p. (Box-folder 25/3)
      - Reprise Never away: act II, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; 5 p. (Box-folder 25/3)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores I], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full scores in ink; Includes: Grandmother's death: #5-a Diploma: #8 After diploma: #8(a) Change to college: #9a [photocopy] [Change of scene]: #15 Vamp to Jennie reads letter; Jennie reads letter: #15-a So far: utility: #20 You are never away: utility: #21 (Box-folder 25/4)
      - [Miscellaneous full scores II], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full scores in ink, and (2) ms. trumpet parts in ink; Includes: [Change after Never away]: no. 23a [3rd trumpet part] That's all, brother: #35. Note: 3rd trumpet part laid in Joe goes to Chicago: #36 Chaser: [exit music]: [#45] The gentleman is a dope: utility (Box-folder 25/5)
      - [Miscellaneous cut music], Arranger's holograph (Bennett) and unidentified ms. full scores in ink; Includes: Change into Wedding Change to cocktail. Note: 3rd trumpet part for "Change to Yatata" laid in A fellow needs a girl: utility Hangover Marjorie's death: #24 [Rotunda]: Beginning Rotunda Sitting on the porch [in the moonlight]/utility [Sitting on the porch in the moonlight]: End of 2d Porch [Sitting on the porch ....]: Into 2d Porch Miscellaneous (4 scores, [1] p. each). Note: titles include "End of Allegro," and "Children's dance" [Unidentified] (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Carousel (1945) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Ballet: act II: #27, Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink & pencil; 90 p. + inserts (p. 33a, 85a), lacking p. 27; Note: Tenor II part in pencil attached to the inside of the accompanying folder; Includes (#'s 1-9): "Nativity" "Louise's dance" "Children's scene" "Snow family" "Youngest Snow" "Carnival" "Seduction" "Mother and daughter" "Children's party" (Box-folder 26/1)
      - Blow high, blow low, Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink & pencil; 24 p. (Box-folder 26/2)
      - The carousel waltz, Printed full score; 56 p.; Arrangement by Don Walker (Box-folder 26/3)
      - Entr'acte, Ms. full score in ink; 38 p. (Box-folder 26/4)
      - Finale act I, Ms. score for reeds and brass (p. a-c) and ms. full score (p. 3-8), in pencil; [9] p. (Box-folder 26/5)
      - Finale act I: new, Ms. full score in pencil; 2 p.; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 26/5)
      - Geraniums [in the winder]: [act II], Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink & pencil; 17 p.; Includes: "There's nothin' so bad for a woman"; Note laid in: "Incomplete! Last 20 bars missing" (Box-folder 26/6)
      - The highest judge of all: [act II], Ms. full score in ink; 21 p. (Box-folder 26/7)
      - Hornpipe :[act I]: #14, Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink; 43 p. + p. a; Note: p. a, in short score form, is titled "Hornpipe vamp" (Box-folder 26/8)
      - If I loved you see: You're a queer one, Julie Jordon
      - June is bustin' out all over, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 31 p. + p. a (title page) (Box-folder 27/1)
      - Julie and Carrie: Mister Snow, Arrangers' holograph (Bennett; Don Walker) full score in ink; p. 1-16, 1-13; Includes: "You're a queer one, Julie Jordan"; Uniform title: Mister Snow (Box-folder 27/2)
      - When I marry Mr. Snow: chorus, Arranger's holograph (Bennett) full score in ink; p. 17-35 + [5] p. (variously paginated); Note enclosed: "Out! Does not match orch parts."; Uniform title: Mister Snow (Box-folder 27/2)
      - Mr. Snow reprise: [act I], Ms. full score in ink & pencils; 18 p. (Box-folder 27/3)
      - Opening act I scene II, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 6 p. (Box-folder 27/4)
      - Opening act II: A real nice clambake, Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) full score in ink; [1] p. (Box-folder 27/5)
      - Opening scene III act II, Ms. full score (incomplete) in ink; p. 2-3; Note: not used in show (Box-folder 27/6)
      - Clambake, Ms. full score in ink; 47 p.; Uniform title: A real nice clambake (Box-folder 27/7)
      - Clambake specialty, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 40 p.; Note: not used in show; Uniform title: A real nice clambake (Box-folder 27/7)
      - Stonecutters cut it on stone = There's nothin' so bad for a woman see: There's nothin' so bad for a woman
      - Storm scene: [act I], Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 19 p.; At top: "Come Be Billy Mounts"; Laid in: ms. conductor's score in ink; 4 p.; On folder: "Out/Finale Act I (Old)" (Box-folder 27/8)
      - There's nothin' so bad for a woman see: Geraniums in the winder
      - What's the use of wondering: [act II], Arranger's holograph (Don Walker) and unidentified ms. (p. 18) full score in ink & pencil; p. 1-10, 13-18; Attached to t.p.: "Does not match orch. parts."; Note: not used in show; Uniform title: What's the use of wond'rin' (Box-folder 28/1)
      - What's the use of wond'rin': reprise, Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 11 p.; Uniform title: What's the use of wond'rin' (Box-folder 28/1)
      - Wondering change: act II: #21, Unidentified ms. (p. 1-6) and arranger's holograph (Don Walker, p. 18-20) full score in ink; [9] p.; Uniform title: What's the use of wond'rin' (Box-folder 28/1)
      - When the children are asleep: [act I], Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) full score in ink; 47 p.; Includes: "Encore" (Box-folder 28/2)
      - You'll never walk alone; Finale tag, Ms. full score in ink & pencil; p. 5-18 + p. 7; Note laid in: "#24/Last 20 bars missing"; Also: empty folder included (Box-folder 28/3)
      - Scene -- "Billy and Julie"; If I loved you, Arrangers' holograph (Don Walker; Hans Spialek [inserts]) full score in ink & pencils; 34 p. + inserts ([9] p.); Uniform title: You're a queer one, Julie Jordon (Box-folder 28/4)
      - Billy -- Julie tag: [act I], Ms. full score in ink & pencil; 6 p.; Uniform title: You're a queer one, Julie Jordon (Box-folder 28/4)
      - You're a queer one, Julie Jordon see: Mister Snow
      - [Miscellaneous full scores], Ms. (Don Walker) short score and unidentified ms. full score in ink; Includes: My little girl incidental: [act II]: #28 Opening graduation scene: [June is busting]: [act II] (Box-folder 28/5)
      - [Miscellaneous unused music], Arranger's holograph (Hans Spialek) and unidentified ms. full scores; Includes: Back to earth: [act II]. Laid in: conductor's score in ink; 2 p. Bill and Julie: interlude #1 Bill and Julie: interlude #2. Note laid in: "This is 'If I loved you' p. 40 in vocal score/Incomplete!" Bill change Death scene. Note: combines "Bill and Julie" interludes I & II From "Judge" to "Walk alone". Note: "Record Version" (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Flower Drum Song (1958) lyrics by Oscar Hammerstein II
      - Ballet see: Ta's dream
      - Chop suey, Arranger's holograph (Joe Glover) full score in ink; 17 p. (Box-folder 29/1)